{
    "subject": "resource/Stacey_Hayes",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/London",
    "human_readable": "The birth place of Stacey Hayes is London.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9884219765663147,
            "question": "Is London the birthplace of Stacey Hayes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9794700145721436,
            "question": "In which country was Stacey Hayes born, assuming London is her birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9330065846443176,
            "question": "Where was Stacey Hayes born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8800259232521057,
            "question": "What city is associated with Stacey Hayes' birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8783591985702515,
            "question": "If Stacey Hayes was born in London, what can you infer about her nationality?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8584575653076172,
            "question": "What city holds a special place in the story of Stacey Hayes' birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7465054988861084,
            "question": "Can you tell me anything about Stacey Hayes' origins based on her birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6432633399963379,
            "question": "What is the significance of London in relation to Stacey Hayes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4732731878757477,
            "question": "What geographical location is significant in Stacey Hayes' early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3034777343273163,
            "question": "If someone wanted to learn more about Stacey Hayes' early life, where would they start their research?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The birth place of Stacey Hayes is London.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7972_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What geographical location is significant in Stacey Hayes' early life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7972_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of London in relation to Stacey Hayes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7972_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me anything about Stacey Hayes' origins based on her birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7972_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7972_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7972_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7972_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7972_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7972_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7972_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7972_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7972_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7972_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7972_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text  \"Stacey Hayes was born on 10 August 1976 in London, England, UK.\" and \"Stacey Hayes is from London, England, UK.\" clearly states that her birthplace is London.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can determine that:\n\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7972/re-ranker-msmarco/64.txt confirms that Stacey Hayes was born in London, England, UK.\n* File_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7972/re-ranker-msmarco/10.txt also confirms that Stacey Hayes was born on August 10, 1976, in London, England, UK.\n\nGiven this information, the triple \"The birth place of Stacey Hayes is London.\" is supported by the documents. Therefore:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Stacey Hayes was born on August 10, 1976, in London, England, UK, which supports the statement that her birthplace is London."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}